Finding Aid for School of Nursing (University of Michigan) records, 1891-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Rhetaugh Dumas
  - Topical Files (), 1961-1999; bulk 1981-1993
    - Nursing Associates in Independent Practice, 1979 (Box 61)
    - Nursing Health Services Administration
      - General, 1980-1983 (Box 62)
      - Advisory Committee, 1983 (Box 62)
    - Nursing History Society, 1982-1994 (Box 62)
    - Nursing Research, 1984-1990 (Box 62)
    - Nursing Research Centers, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Nursing Research Core Center Grant Proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 62)
    - Nursing Shortage
      - Fact Sheets, 1987 (Box 62)
      - Organizational Response, 1988 (Box 62)
    - Nutrition, 1980-1982 (Box 62)
    - Occupational Health Nursing, 1983-1993; 4 folders (Box 62)
    - Off-Campus Programs, 1992 (Box 62)
    - On Job On Campus (OJOC) Program, 1992-1994 (Box 62)
    - Operational Plan, 1988-1990 (Box 62)
    - Organizational Charts, 1980-1993 (Box 62)
    - Organizational Charts (suggestions for restructuring), 1980-1982 (Box 62)
    - Organizational Planning and Support, Associate Dean for, 1990-1994 (Box 62)
    - Other Colleges and Universities
      - Eastern Michigan University, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Emory University, 1981-1989 (Box 62)
      - Jackson Community College, 1991 (Box 62)
      - Michigan State University, 1981-1990 (Box 62)
      - Saginaw Valley State University, 1986-1991 (Box 62)
      - Tuskegee University, 1983-1986 (Box 62)
      - University of California-San Francisco, 1989 (Box 62)
      - University of Washington, 1988 (Box 62)
      - Washtenaw Community College, 1990 (Box 62)
      - Wayne State University, 1983-1989 (Box 62)
      - Yale University, 1981-1992 (Box 62)
      - Proposed Degree Programs, 1985-1994 (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1993 (Box 62)
    - Parent-Child Nursing
      - General
        - 1981-1992 (Box 63)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 63)
      - Annual Meetings, 1985-1991 (Box 63)
      - Area Meetings, 1982-1986 (Box 63)
      - Differential Treatment of Minority Applicants, 1991 (Box 63)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1984-1992; 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1987 (Box 63)
      - Neonatal/Pediatric Critical Care Track, 1988 (Box 63)
      - Rural Nursing Practicum, 1982 (Box 63)
    - People to People International, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
    - Peer List, 1987-1988 (Box 63)
    - Pharmacy Course, 1993-1994 (Box 63)
    - Plastination Laboratory Development Project, 1987 (Box 63)
    - Policy on Classified Research, 1986 (Box 63)
    - Postdoctoral Training Program, 1988 (Box 63)
    - President, Office of, 1979-1993 (Box 63)
    - Presidential Inauguration, 1988 (Box 63)
    - Presidential Initiatives Fund, 1987 (Box 63)
    - Presidential Transition Briefing, 1988 (Box 63)
    - President's Advisory Commission on Minority Affairs, 1989-1992 (Box 63)
    - President's Advisory Commission on Women's Issues, 1989-1992 (Box 63)
    - Presidents Council of State Colleges and Universities, 1980 (Box 63)
    - Primary Care Nursing, 1979-1982 (Box 63)
    - Professional Nurse Traineeship, 1992-1994 (Box 63)
    - Profile, 1987-1988 (Box 63)
    - Program Chairs Meetings, 1984-1990; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Program on Conflict Management Alternatives, 1987-1988 (Box 63)
    - Program Reviews, 1992; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Protocol for International Visitors, 1992 (Box 63)
    - Provost, Office of
      - General
        - Whitaker, 1991-1993 (Box 63)
        - Vest, 1989-1990 (Box 63)
        - Duderstadt, 1986-1988 (Box 63)
        - Frye, 1979-1986; 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Academic Year Review, 1991-1994 (Box 63)
      - Assistant Vice President, 1987-1993 (Box 63)
      - Associate Provost, 1987-1994 (Box 63)
      - Associate Vice President, 1983-1988 (Box 63)
      - Charles Vest Farewell, 1990 (Box 63)
      - Commission on Minority Recruitment, Retention, and Graduation, 1991 (Box 63)
      - Deans Retreat, 1991 (Box 63)
      - Development Office Assessment, 1990-1993 (Box 63)
      - James Duderstadt Farewell, 1988 (Box 63)
      - Mandate Encouraging Transfer Agreement for Scholars of Color (META), 1992-1993 (Box 63)
      - Research Incentive Program I, 1989-1993 (Box 63)
      - Research Incentive Program II, 1989-1992 (Box 63)
      - Research Incentive Program III, 1992 (Box 63)
      - Salary Equity Study, 1989 (Box 63)
      - Vice Provost for Minority Affairs
        - General, 1987-1993 (Box 63)
        - Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 63)
        - Historically and Predominantly Black Colleges, 1987-1992 (Box 63)
        - King/Chavez/Parks Visiting Scholar Program
          - 1990-1992 (Box 63)
          - 1987-1990 (Box 63)
      - Vice Provost for Multicultural Affairs, 1992-1994 (Box 64)
    - Psychiatric Care in Prisons, 1994 (Box 64)
    - Psychiatric Mental Health Nursing
      - General, 1981-1991; 2 folders (Box 64)
      - Annual Meetings, 1985-1991 (Box 64)
      - Area Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 64)
      - External Review
        - General, 1987 (Box 64)
        - Background Material, 1984-1987; 2 folders (Box 64)
        - C.V.s of Faculty, 1987 (Box 64)
        - Report and Corrections, 1987 (Box 64)
      - Faculty and Student Issues, 1984-1988 (Box 73)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2063 ]
      - Graduate Program Revision, 1986 (Box 64)
      - Revision of National Standards of Psychiatric and Mental Health Nursing, 1982 (Box 64)
      - Task Force, 1987 (Box 64)
    - Public Health, School of
      - General, 1984-1994 (Box 64)
      - Collaborative Clinical Trials Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 64)
      - Delivery System of Long-Term Care, 1987 (Box 64)
      - Reception for Avedis Donabedian, 1988 (Box 64)
      - Robert Wood Johnson/PEW Proposal, 1989 (Box 64)
    - Questionnaire on Objectives of Academic Units, 1976 (Box 64)
    - Racism, 1987-1994 (Box 64)
    - Rackham, School of Graduate Studies
      - General
        - 1985-1993 (Box 64)
        - 1980-1982 (Box 64)
      - 50th Birthday, 1988 (Box 64)
      - Minority Faculty Development, 1992 (Box 64)
      - Review
        - Area Responses, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 64)
        - Correspondence with Rackham, 1982-1985 (Box 64)
        - Dean's Response, 1982-1983 (Box 64)
        - Doctoral Program, 1978-1981; 2 folders (Box 64)
        - Faculty Response, 1982 (Box 65)
        - Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1981 (Box 65)
        - Master's Programs Reviews, 1981 (Box 65)
        - Meeting with Rackham Executive Board, 1982 (Box 65)
        - Response to Recommendations, 1983 (Box 65)
        - Response to Recommendations-Drafts, 1981-1983 (Box 65)
    - Recommendations for the Next Decade, 1972-1982 (Box 65)
    - Reduction in Freshmen Class, 1981 (Box 65)
    - Registered Care Technologist Proposal, 1988 (Box 65)
    - Reorganization, 1981-1982 (Box 65)
    - Report from the Dean, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Research, Vice President for
      - General, 1985-1994 (Box 65)
      - Committees, 1986-1992 (Box 65)
      - Diversity Symposium, 1988 (Box 65)
      - Meeting, November 12, 1987 (Box 65)
    - Research Area, 1980-1981 (Box 65)
    - Resource Documents, 1979-1985 (Box 65)
    - RN Studies
      - General
        - 1986-1992 (Box 65)
        - 1980-1982 (Box 65)
      - Annual Meetings, 1985-1993 (Box 65)
      - Area Meetings, 1988-1992 (Box 65)
      - Program in Kalamazoo, 1982 (Box 65)
    - Reunion of Black Graduates, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Saginaw Valley State University Agreement, 1992 (Box 65)
    - School of Nursing
      - Administration and Organizational Charts, 1987-1988 (Box 65)
      - Evaluation Plan, 1989-1992 (Box 65)
      - Logo, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1982-1994 (Box 65)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1988-1993 (Box 65)
    - Shapiro Scrapbook, 1987 (Box 65)
    - Single Master's Degree (proposed), 1986 (Box 65)
    - Social, Economic and Political Consequences of Mental Illness, undated (Box 65)
    - Social Work, School of, 1987-1991 (Box 65)
    - South African Career Development Program, 1991 (Box 65)
    - South African Delegation, 1990 (Box 65)
    - Specialist in Aging Certificate Program, 1984-1987 (Box 65)
    - Speeches and Presentations
      - 1994
        - Student Recognition Awards Ceremony (Box 65)
      - 1993
        - Orientations (Box 65)
        - Staff Recognition Luncheon (Box 65)
        - State of the School Address (Box 65)
        - Student Recognition and Awards Ceremony (Box 65)
      - 1992
        - New Faculty Orientation (Box 65)
        - Presentation About Sabbatical Year at the Jung Institute in Switzerland (audiocassette) (Box 65)
      - 1991
        - Convocation (Box 65)
        - December Graduation (Box 65)
        - Staff Recognition Luncheon (Box 65)
        - State of the School Address (Box 65)
      - 1990
        - All School Dinner (Box 65)
        - Doctoral Student Orientation (Box 65)
        - Faculty Research Day (Box 65)
        - Master's Student Orientation (Box 65)
        - New Faculty Orientation (Box 65)
        - "1990-1991 Agenda for the School of Nursing," U-M Medical Center Nursing Executive Council (Box 65)
        - Parents Weekend (Box 65)
        - Staff Recognition Luncheon, 2 folders (Box 65)
        - State of the School Address (Box 65)
      - 1989
        - Convocation (Box 65)
        - Dean's Message for School of Nursing Bulletin (Box 65)
        - Faculty Meeting (Box 65)
        - Faculty Research Day (Box 65)
        - Graduation (Box 65)
        - Michigan Nursing Students Association (Box 65)
        - Nursing Research Roundtable (Box 65)
        - Open House (Box 65)
        - Orientations (Box 65)
        - Post-Baccalaureate Medical Program Completion Ceremony (Box 65)
        - State of the School Address (Box 65)
      - 1988
        - Clinical Simulation Lab Ribbon Cutting (Box 65)
        - Convocation (Box 65)
        - Faculty Research Day (Box 65)
        - Future for Women at the University of Michigan (Box 65)
        - Graduate Student Nursing Research Symposium (Box 65)
        - New Faculty Orientation (Box 65)
        - Orientation and Medical Center Alumni Society (Box 65)
        - Orientation for Master's Students (Box 65)
        - State of the School Address (Box 65)
      - 1987
        - AIDS Conference (Box 65)
        - Convocation (Box 65)
        - Doctoral Student Orientation (Box 65)
        - Master's Student Orientation (Box 65)
        - New Faculty Orientation (Box 65)
        - "Nursing in the 21st Century," University Seminar (Box 65)
        - Staff Recognition Luncheon (Box 65)
        - State of the School Address (Box 65)
      - 1986
        - Convocation (Box 66)
        - Faculty Orientation (Box 66)
        - Master's Student Orientation (Box 66)
        - "Preparing Adults for Leadership Roles in the 1980s and 1990s," National Nursing Conference on Leadership (Box 66)
        - State of the School Address (Box 66)
      - 1985
        - "Celebrating Excellence" School of Pharmacy Honors Banquet (Box 66)
        - Convocation (Box 66)
        - Faculty Research Symposium (Box 66)
        - Graduate Open House (Box 66)
        - Graduate Student Research Symposium (Box 66)
        - Master's Student Orientation (Box 66)
        - Michigan League for Nursing Annual Meeting (Box 66)
        - New Faculty Orientation (Box 66)
        - "Nursing in the Year 2000," University Seminar (Box 66)
        - "Social and Health Needs of Aging Blacks" (Box 66)
      - 1984
        - Class Presentation to Nursing 671 (Box 66)
        - Convocation (Box 66)
        - Medical Center Alumni Society Visiting Committee (Box 66)
        - Open House (Box 66)
        - "Political Issues in Nursing," Michigan Nurse Week (Box 66)
        - Striping Ceremony (Box 66)
      - 1983
        - Convocation Address (Box 66)
        - Faculty Research Symposium (Box 66)
        - Open House (Box 66)
        - Research Symposium Opening Remarks (Box 66)
        - State of the School Address (Box 66)
        - Striping Ceremony (Box 66)
        - Toast for Graduating Seniors (Box 66)
      - 1982
        - State of the School Address (Box 66)
        - Striping Ceremony (Box 66)
      - 1980-1981
        - Psychiatric Nursing (Box 66)
      - Slides for Speeches, 1986-1988 (Box 66)
    - Sponsored Funds Reports
      - 1992-1993 (Box 66)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 66)
    - Staff Evaluation Forms, 1992 (Box 66)
    - Strategic Planning
      - General, 1988-1992 (Box 66)
      - Options-Faculty Responses, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Retreat, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 66)
      - Strategic Review, 1988 (Box 66)
    - Striping Ceremony, 1983-1984 (Box 66)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for, 1983-1992 (Box 66)
    - Student Affairs (School of Nursing)
      - General, 1977-1994 (Box 66)
      - Assistant Director of School Admissions, 1991-1992 (Box 66)
      - Financial Aid, 1987-1988 (Box 66)
      - Proposal for a Marketing Approach to Student Recruitment, 1986 (Box 66)
    - Student Financial Aid Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 66)
    - Student Loan Delinquencies, 1984-1986 (Box 66)
    - Student Loan Program-Annual Operating Report, 1988 (Box 66)
    - Student Records, 1977-1984 (Box 66)
    - Student Recruitment
      - General (Box 66)
      - Student Surveys, 1988 (Box 66)
    - Study Abroad, 1992 (Box 66)
    - Study of Quality Indicators of Nursing Doctoral Programs, 1984 (Box 66)
    - Summer Institute for Women in Higher Education Administration, 1983 (Box 66)
    - Support Network for Affirmative Action Programs (SNAPP), 1981-1982 (Box 66)
    - Survey of Black Faculty and Graduate Students, 1989 (Box 66)
    - Task Force for Statistical Support, 1988-1990 (Box 66)
    - Task Force on HIV Positive Students in the Health Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 66)
    - Task Force on Undergraduate Admissions, 1986 (Box 66)
    - Task Force on Violence Against Women, 1993-1994 (Box 66)
    - Taubman Medical Library
      - General, 1980-1991 (Box 66)
      - Medline, 1989-1994 (Box 66)
    - Telecommunications, 1988 (Box 66)
    - Ten Year Goal Plans from Areas, 1983 (Box 66)
    - Tenure, 1986 (Box 66)
    - Transplant Policy Center, 1985-1988 (Box 66)
    - Undergraduate Coordinators Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 50)
    - Undergraduate Education Workshop, 1994 (Box 67)
    - Undergraduate Financial Aid, 1983 (Box 67)
    - Undergraduate Initiatives Fund, 1987 (Box 67)
    - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP), 1991-1992 (Box 67)
    - Undergraduate Student Address List, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Undergraduate Studies
      - General, 1984-1991 (Box 67)
      - Area Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 67)
      - Diversity in Design: The Undergraduate Program, 1989 (Box 67)
      - Management Course, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Undergraduate Studies/Graduate Studies Workshop, 1992-1994 (Box 67)
    - United States
      - Department of Health and Human Services
        - General, 1983-1987 (Box 67)
        - Division of Nursing, 1984-1993 (Box 67)
        - National Cancer Advisory Board, 1985 (Box 67)
        - National Center for Nursing Research
          - General, 1988-1990 (Box 67)
          - Search Committee for Director, 1986 (Box 67)
      - Federal Government, undated (Box 67)
      - Legislature
        - General
          - 1989-1994 (Box 67)
          - 1987-1988 (Box 67)
          - 1982-1986 (Box 67)
        - Gramm-Rudman Amendment, 1986 (Box 67)
        - Hurdis Griffith, 1987 (Box 67)
        - Daniel Inouye
          - 1988-1989 (Box 67)
          - 1987 (Box 67)
          - 1986 (Box 67)
          - 1985 (Box 67)
          - 1984 (Box 67)
          - 1983 (Box 67)
          - 1981-1982 (Box 67)
        - National Institute of Mental Health, 1982-1990 (Box 67)
        - Nurse Training Act, 1984-1985 (Box 67)
        - Carl Pursell, 1981-1991 (Box 67)
        - Student Loan Program, 1982-1984 (Box 67)
        - Testimony on Health Appropriations, 1983 (Box 67)
    - University Council on International Academic Affairs (UCIAA), 1988-1991 (Box 67)
    - University Events, Office of, 1990 (Box 67)
    - University Hospitals
      - Adjunct Appointment Nominations, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Chief of Nursing Affairs
        - General, 1989-1993 (Box 67)
        - Search, 1993-1994 (Box 67)
      - Clinical Affairs, Assistant Dean for
        - 1987-1989 (Box 68)
        - 1980-1987 (Box 68)
      - Clinical Research Center, 1988-1989 (Box 68)
      - Consultants' Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 68)
      - Director of Nursing, 1988-1993 (Box 68)
      - Executive Director, 1980-1993 (Box 68)
      - Facilities Naming Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 68)
      - Joint Staff, 1989-1994 (Box 68)
      - Master of Science in Anesthesia Proposal, 1982-1985 (Box 68)
      - Nurses' Strike, 1989-1992 (Box 68)
      - Nurses' Strike-Fact Finder's Report, 1990 (Box 68)
      - Nurses Survey, 1980-1981 (Box 68)
      - Nursing Executive Council, 1980-1992 (Box 68)
      - Nursing Reorganization, 1979-1981 (Box 68)
      - Nursing Services, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Operating Rooms, 1986 (Box 68)
      - Process for Review for Adjunct Appointments, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Psychiatric Nursing, 1984-1989 (Box 68)
      - Replacement Hospital Project, 1980-1988 (Box 68)
      - Senior Associate Director, 1990 (Box 68)
      - Standardization of Procedures Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 68)
      - Surgical Nursing, 1982-1986 (Box 68)
      - Transformation Plans, 1988 (Box 68)
    - University Reaccreditation, 1979-1989 (Box 68)
    - University Relations, Office of, 1990-1994 (Box 68)
    - University Seminars, 1985-1991 (Box 68)
    - Upjohn Proposal for Graduate Nursing Fellowships, 1987-1990 (Box 68)
    - U.S. Exchanges, 1988 (Box 68)
    - Venture Team, 1992-1993 (Box 68)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital
      - General, 1976-1993 (Box 68)
      - Deans Committee, 1979-1989; 3 folders (Box 68)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1989-1991 (Box 68)
    - Women of Color Task Force Career Conference, 1988-1991 (Box 68)
    - Women in Science Program, 1981-1988 (Box 68)
    - Women's Initiative Group (WING), 1987 (Box 68)
    - Women's Research Club, 1981-1982 (Box 68)
    - Women's Studies Program, 1984 (Box 68)
  - Facilities Files (Unprocessed)
    The Facilities Files series, 1977-1990 (2.5 linear feet), is unprocessed, and contains correspondence, architectural plans, reports, and memos related to many aspects of the refurbishment of part of the old St. Joseph's Hospital as the School of Nursing's new facility at 400 North Ingalls Street. Also included is a small amount of material related to the school's previous facility in the Medical Science complex.
    - [Unprocessed files]
      - [Unprocessed files] (Box 69)
      - [Unprocessed files] (Box 70)
        (continued)
      - [Unprocessed files] (Box 71)
- Dean Ada Sue Hinshaw
  - Health Services Research Initiative Task Force
    The records of Dean Ada Sue Hinshaw will likely grow when future accessions are received, but for now are held in one series, Health Services Research Initiative Task Force, 1996 (0.75 linear feet). The series contains the records of a university-wide task force Hinshaw chaired that focused on developing strategies to support faculty conducting health services research throughout the university, with an eye to establishing a multidisciplinary institute. Included are meeting minutes and supporting materials, faculty profiles, and drafts of and comments on the task force's final report.
    - Faculty Profiles, 1996; 2 folders (Box 72)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2022 ]
    - Final Report
      - Report, October 1996 (Box 72)
      - Penultimate Draft, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Draft 2, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Draft 2 Comments, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Draft 1, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Draft 1 Comments, 1996; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Literature Searches, 1996 (Box 72)
    - Organizational Materials (include member list, meeting minutes and interim report), 1996; 4 folders (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 72)
  - Office and Division Files
    The Office and Division Files (1991-2000) contain correspondence, memos, and other records detailing the activities of the various offices and divisions within the School of Nursing.
    - School of Nursing history, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Academic Affairs, Office of
      - General, 1994-1997; 4 folders (Box 74)
      - Academic & Student affairs committee meeting, 1999-2000 (Box 74)
      - Honors task force, 1997-2000 (Box 74)
      - 19-month program, 1995 (Box 74)
      - Program directors meeting, 1998-1999 (Box 74)
      - Undergraduate forum, February 18, 1998 (Box 74)
    - Business and Financial Affairs, Office of
      - General, 1994-1997; 2 folders (Box 74)
      - Outside employment guidelines/conflict of interest, 1978-1990 (Box 74)
      - Renovation expenses (Box 74)
      - University Representatives for Step 2 & 3 of the GEO grievance procedure (Box 74)
      - Voice mail (Box 74)
    - Center for Nursing Research
      - General, 1994-1997; 4 folders (Box 74)
      - Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 74)
    - Division II (Division of Health Promotion and Risk Reduction Programs), 1994-1997; 4 folders (Box 75)
    - Doctoral Office
      - General, 1993-1998; 5 folders (Box 75)
      - Doctoral conference, 1995; 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Doctoral forum, 1995; 1997; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Office of International Affairs
      - General, 1996 (Box 75)
      - MUCIA Global, 1998 (Box 75)
      - World Health Organization collaboration, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Office of Multicultural Affairs
      - Minority enrollment, 1990-1997 (Box 75)
      - Multicultural affairs advisory meeting, 1994-1997 (Box 75)
      - KCP Visiting Scholar, 1997 (Box 75)
      - Asian Pacific American (APA) heritage month, 1997-1998 (Box 75)
    - Office of Student Affairs
      - General, 1994 (Box 75)
      - Student handbook, 1999 (Box 75)
  - Topical Files, 1991-1999
    - 1991-1999
      The Topical Files (1991-1999, 12 linear feet) cover many of the different programs, initiatives, activities, reports, policies and procedures, and issues of the School of Nursing.
      - Academic Affairs
        - Academic Affairs Baccalaureate Program, 1995 (Box 76)
        - Academic Affairs Undergrad Program, 1994-1997 (Box 76)
        - Director, Undergraduate and Non-traditional programs, 1995 (Box 76)
        - Handbooks, 2001-2002 (Box 76)
      - Accreditation
        - Commission on Collegiate Nursing, 1996-1998; 3 folders (Box 76)
        - Accreditation site visit, September-October 1993 (Box 76)
      - Administrative Council, 1996-1998; 3 folders (Box 76)
      - Adjunct faculty, 1994 (Box 76)
      - AFSCME employees, 1995 (Box 76)
      - AHEC initiative, 1994 (Box 76)
      - Alcohol and drug policy, 1993; 1997 (Box 76)
      - American Heart Walk, 1999 (Box 76)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1991/1992-1993/1994, 3 folders (Box 76)
        - 1994/1995-1997/1998, 5 folders (Box 77)
      - Arbor Hospice, 1998 (Box 77)
      - Army ROTC "Centers of Excellence,", 1998 (Box 77)
      - Associate Dean job descriptions, 1994 (Box 77)
      - Aw It Haw Foundation
        - General (Box 77)
        - Visit, March 24, 1997 (Box 77)
      - Awards, 1993-1997 (Box 77)
      - Budget
        - 1993-1996, 6 folders (Box 77)
        - 1996-1997
          - Budget (Box 78)
          - Draft document, 3 folders (Box 78)
        - 1997-1998
          - Allocation (Box 78)
          - Materials, 2 folders (Box 78)
          - Plan, 2 folders (Box 78)
        - 1998-1999
          - Budget (Box 78)
          - Papers (Box 78)
          - Fiscal Year, 1999 (Box 78)
        - Budget commitments, 1997-1998 (Box 78)
        - Budget long-term, 1998 (Box 78)
        - Long range planning meeting with Provost, 1998 (Box 78)
      - By-laws, 1998 (Box 78)
      - C-case, 1998 (Box 78)